Awesome, at this point you have completed localizing the text
Ótimo! A essa altura você terminou de localizar o texto
in the just Java app.
no aplicativo Java.
Hopefully you've seen that with just a few modifications,
Talvez tenha visto que com apenas algumas modificações
you can open up your app to whole new audiences.
pode abrir seu aplicativo para um público totalmente novo.
Let's review our solution.
Vamos revisar nossa solução.
Here's the strings.xml file
Aqui está o arquivo strings.xml,
where we pulled out all the possible strings in our app.
onde achamos todos as strings possíveis para nosso app.
For each string resource we provide a comment and
Para cada recurso string fornecemos um comentário
a character limit to help the translator figure out the right translation.
e um limite de caracteres para ajudar o tradutor a fazer a melhor tradução.
In our layout now we refer to string resources.
Nosso layout agora remete a recursos string.
There are no more warnings from Android Studio about hard coding
Não há mais avisos do Android Studio sobre strings em hard code no nosso layout.
And here's a Spanish version of the strings.xml file
Aqui está a versão em espanhol do arquivo strings.xml
with all their Spanish translations.
com as traduções em espanhol.
If you open up the translations editor you can see the name of the string
Se abrir o editor de traduções, verá o nome dos recursos string,
resources, the English translations, as well as the Spanish translations.
as traduções em inglês e em espanhol.
Then in our layout file we can refer to all of these string resources.
Então nosso arquivo de layout pode remeter a esses recursos string.
And now Android Studio doesn't have any more warnings about hard coding
E agora Android Studio não tem mais avisos sobre strings hard code em nosso layout.
Within our Java code we also refer to these string resources.
No nosso código Java também remetemos a esses recursos string.
Note that we also get the local currency with this line of code here.
Observe que também obtemos a moeda local com esta linha de código.
This is a utility function that formats the input price into the current c for
Esta é uma função utilitária que formata o preço para a moeda
the current local.
do local atual.
All of the solution code is linked in instructor notes below.
O link do código resolvido está nas notas do instrutor abaixo.
Gran trabajo, great job.
Buen trabajo! Ótimo trabalho.
Now let's explore further about what else can be done
Agora vamos explorar mais sobre o que pode ser feito
with resources in Android.
com recursos no Android.